All right, the first thing that we
notice about these new skimmers is the
bottom of these ports are glue
connections, but yet they send you two
threaded plugs.
So, I'm guessing that means that we
screw those in from the top side.
That must be what we do. Well, so we'll
screw it in from the top side. Can I see
that spa removal tool?
Does that work? Here, flip it around the
other way. Does that fit in there? All
right, so we'll be able to tighten that
from the top side.
>> [snorts]
>> So, it's kind of like how a fiberglass
skimmer goes.
And then in here we'll glue a And in
here we'll glue a reducer.
All right, so now
So, now they sent Now, here's the thing
that I don't like about these skimmers,
and this is like a big mess up on their
end, in my opinion, but they send these
spacers.
Right here. All right, so those just
kind of go in and they
they clip in.
And it's recessed a little bit for the
thickness of of a steel panel.
But then the mounting screws that they
provide
aren't long enough.
>> Outrageous.
>> And uh
they send you a bag of screws.
I have one bag of screws in the truck,
but
but basically
these screws
need to be
uh well, the mounting screws anyway.
They send you two bags, but they they
send you these two little screws that
are like
a half inch in diameter or something
like that.
They don't go They won't fit. They don't
go through. So, it's like The skimmers
are good, but they're just they're
sending the wrong hardware.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Yes, sir.
>> And I think a lot of a lot of crews are
going to be on site. Like like, for
instance, our South Carolina operation,
the the manager calls me up, and she's
like, "Hey, what's going on?" Because my
guys are out there, and
uh they're saying the screws are too
short. And I was like, "They are?"
Hayward's providing
the wrong hardware for these skimmers.
So, then Hayward needs to get that
together in my opinion.
Because
it's not right.
You can't expect guys to be smart and
figure it out on their own.
You know what I'm saying?
All right, we're about to find out
everybody, but we got these stainless
screws size 14
an inch and a half long, okay?
So, now these
as you see
are longer to fit in and you know, just
enough so that we'll get a grab, okay?
The number The number 12s The number 12s
aren't going to work, okay everybody?
So, don't buy
the number 12s. See, it just goes in
like that. It just goes in.
So, you're not grabbing any threads,
okay? So, don't grab the size 12s
like I did. But, I wasn't sure.
So, size 14
inch and a half and we're going to
hope that that works. We'll let you
know. We did get the skimmer installed.
But, you know
take a peek
from the inside.
Hello, I'm Steve got a pool. I don't
know.
I'm just being silly.